JUSTIN BECKER

Twin Lake, MI 49457

linkedin.com/in/justin-becker-dev

Junior Software Developer (RPG)

I'm a dedicated professional with a diverse skillset and over a decade of experience in patient, student, and customer-facing roles. I'm seeking to utilize my programming knowledge and creativity as a junior developer on the IBMi platform. I thrive on learning new technologies and skills, with a particular interest in the modernization of IBMi/iSeries/AS400 software.

Skill Highlights:

- RPG ILE/Free Form/SQLRPGLE
- Access Client Solutions
- Rational Developer for i
- Java Development
- C# Development
- SQL Server, MySQL
- JavaScript, PHP, CSS, HTML
- Agile/Scrum/Waterfall SDLC
- Detailed Documentation

Experience

Junior Programmer Analyst – 2024 to Present **Developer Intern** – 2024 to 2024 **Session Musician / Audio Engineer** – 2021 to 2024 Cardiac Telemetry Specialist – 2020 to 2021 Level III Pharmacy Tech / Liaison – 2018 to 2020 Pharmacy Technician – 2016 to 2018 College Tutor / Administrative Aid – 2012 – 2016

Junior Programmer Analyst | Innovative Software Solutions inc. | Remote

- Developed RPGLE maintenance programs for legacy IBMi-based software.
- Web/mobile development and API integration.
- Continuing education in new languages and frameworks.

Intern | CDR Software | Remote

- Provided technical support for iSeries-based software suite designed for managing distribution operations.
- Identified deficiencies in documentation and worked with technical writers to resolve them.
- Used critical thinking and investigation skills to identify solutions to customer issues which lacked sufficient documentation.

Session Musician / Audio Engineer | Freelance | Remote

- Developed and sustained a client base through strategic marketing on digital platforms and leveraging personal networks.
- Engaged in collaborative projects with producers, composers, and fellow musicians to create original songs and arrangements.
- Specialized in bespoke composition, delivering tailor-made songs to meet diverse client specifications.
- Offered comprehensive audio engineering services, encompassing mixing, mastering, audio editing, and sound design, utilizing professional equipment and software.

Cardiac Telemetry Technician | Trinity Health Hospital | Muskegon, MI

- Served as a vital member of a healthcare team which consisted of over 20 professionals and specialists.
- Interpreted and documented patient heart rhythms, including dysrhythmias, using ECG technology and specialized software.
- Alerted resuscitation teams to assist patients experiencing life -threatening dysrhythmias or critical changes in vital signs.
- Sanitized medical equipment in accordance with hospital infection control procedures.

Level III Pharmacy Technician | Trinity Health Pharmacy | Muskegon, MI

- Coordinated with teams of over 25 professionals consisting of physicians, pharmacists, and RN
 case managers to determine optimal medication regimen for each unique patient circumstance.
- Conducted formulary queries and adjudication with insurance companies to ensure financial sustainability for patient medication therapies.
- Educated patients and caregivers on medication usage, side effects, and interactions.

Pharmacy Technician | Trinity Health Pharmacy / Meijer Pharmacy | Muskegon, MI

- Ordered, received, and shelved pharmacy inventory.
- Transcribed prescriptions given over the phone by medical practitioners.
- Conducted point-of-sale transactions and reconciliation.

College Tutor / Administrative Aid | Muskegon Community College | Muskegon, MI

- Provided administrative support to faculty in the College Success Center.
- Tutored college students in subjects such as statistics, math, and English composition.
- Responsible for proctoring student exams.

Achievements

1st place winner of WMCPA's iCON2024 student RPG programming competition | Muskegon Community College

Advanced to Pharmacy Liaison within 3 years, pioneering a new role in the organization which increased Meds to Go program utilization by over 50% | Trinity Health Pharmacy

Trained as an Epic Systems super user and assisted in facilitating nationwide EMR transition | Trinity Health Pharmacy

Selected for a position as a Student Liaison on the COMMON Education Foundation board where my input was used to shape student outreach strategies.

Recipient of Muskegon Community College's 2024 Award for Excellence in Software Development. | Muskegon Community College

Developed and implemented an orientation program for new technicians to ensure consistency in processes, which promoted both efficiency and patient safety | Trinity Health Pharmacy

Education

Muskegon Community College • Software development with a focus on RPG | Education | Nursing

COMMON • Associate Application Developer Certification

Muskegon Community College • Midrange Programming Certification

Meijer Pharmacy Technician Training Program • Pharmacy Technician License

Technology Summary

Languages RPG ILE/RPG IV, SQL, DDS, CL, HTML5, JavaScript, PHP, CSS, Java, C, C++, C#

Development Tools Eclipse Rational Developer (RDI), Visual Studio, VSCode, phpMyAdmin, SQL

Server Management Studio, Android Studio, JavaFX Scene Builder, Unity, Reaper,

FL Studio

Supporting Tools Microsoft Suite, Access Client Solutions, Atlassian JIRA, Autotask, WordPress,

GitHub